Kasey Chang

San Francisco, California, United States



linkedin.com/in/kasey-chang



guyreviews77-hired@yahoo.com

Summary

Fullstack Engineer with BSEE/CS trained in HTML5/ CSS3/ JS/ jQuery/ Node.js / and more, with experience in database and web development and IT Support, plus education in data science and applied AI.

Google IT Support certificate holder

IT Automation with Python certificate holder

IBM Data Science Specialization certificate holder

IBM IT Fundamentals for Cybersecurity certificate holder

Experience

Delivery Driver

Imperfect Foods

Jul 2018 - Jan 2020 (1 year 7 months)

Delivery from warehouse to consumer, up to 105 orders per day all over SF Bay Area, from Novato to San Jose, from San Francisco to Vallejo, Discovery Bay, and Livermore, and everywhere in between with fullsize 12 ft cargo van, in all weather conditions, on all kinds of roads (including dirt roads off Portola Valley, to city streets)

Dispatcher, Backoffice Support, Customer Service

ACE XPRESS CHARTER

Jan 2002 - Sep 2017 (15 years 9 months)

Do a little of everything in a small bus charter company except driving the buses. Collect payment, responding to customer inquiries, book charter orders, talk with vendors, order parts, schedule maintenance. complete compliance paperwork, respond to emergencies and urgencies.



Information Technology Support Specialist

DCL Logistics

Jan 1994 - Jan 2004 (10 years 1 month)

Generalist troubleshooter, and later, software engineer, maintained network at multiple locations, upgraded from a multi-user desktop database to SQL server with GUI frontend, custom-wrote assembly line QC system, worked on various projects, assisted in migration to ERP, and much much more.

Education



San Francisco State University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Electrical and Electronics Engineering

1992 - 1994

Minor in Computer Science, degreeVerified

Licenses & Certifications

- Google IT Support Specialization Coursera
 9LZTXXTZSDJV
- IBM Data Science Specialization Coursera
 V53AL32UTWAZ
- IT Fundamentals for Cybersecurity Specialization Coursera
 V6TXWG7PCTKA
- Google IT Automation with Python Coursera

Honors & Awards

â Sage (rank 36) - GameFAQs.com

Sage is one of the three almost mythical ranks for contributors of the most widely read FAQs. Only the staff and industry professionals have higher user levels. See https://gamefaqs.gamespot.com/help/18-board-basics

Skills

Problem Solving • Technical Support • Customer Service • Transportation • Information Technology • Network Administration • Computer Science • Desktop Computers • Python (Programming Language) • Computer Literacy